<!-- Learn Flex Start -->
<div class="row-fluid">
  <!-- Project -->
  <div class="span2">
    <div class="picture">
      <a href="http://www.slideshare.net/bigosmallm/flexjs-an-introduction">
        <img src="img/training-flex-introduction.png" alt=""/>
        <div class="image-overlay-link"></div>
      </a>
    </div>
    <div class="item-description">
      <h5>
        <a href="http://www.slideshare.net/bigosmallm/flexjs-an-introduction">FlexJS - An Introduction</a>
      </h5>
      <p>FlexJS™ is a new application development framework that cross compiles MXML and ActionScript into HTML and JavaScript. It runs in web, desktop and mobile(app) in swf format and runs in
        browser based environments as HTML/JS/CSS files without the need for the Flash Player plugin. It brings the advantages of Flex to the JavaScript world.
      </p>
    </div>
  </div>

  <!-- Project -->
  <div class="span2">
    <div class="picture">
      <a href="http://www.adobe.com/devnet/flex/videotraining/exercises/ex1_01.html">
        <img src="img/training-flex-in-a-week.png" alt=""/>
        <div class="image-overlay-link"></div>
      </a>
    </div>
    <div class="item-description">
      <h5>
        <a href="http://www.adobe.com/devnet/flex/videotraining/exercises/ex1_01.html">The Flex in a Week Series</a>
      </h5>
      <p>The Flex in a Week training series consists of videos and exercises to teach experienced programmers how to program using the Flex 4.5 framework and Flash Builder 4.5. To gain the most from
        this series, watch the videos and complete the exercises in the order in which they are listed.
      </p>
    </div>
  </div>

  <!-- Project -->
  <div class="span2">
    <div class="picture">
      <a href="http://www.adobe.com/devnet/flex/videotraining.html">
        <img src="img/training-flex-in-a-week-video.png" alt=""/>
        <div class="image-overlay-link"></div>
      </a>
    </div>
    <div class="item-description">
      <h5>
        <a href="http://www.adobe.com/devnet/flex/videotraining.html">Flex In A Week Video Series</a>
      </h5>
      <p>The Flex in a Week video training course will help you understand how you can leverage the open source Flex framework to build RIAs. To make it easier for you to learn Flex, you will use the
        Eclipse-based Flash Builder 4.5 development tool, which includes the Flex framework and provides features such as intelligent coding, interactive step-through debugging, and visual design of
        the user layout.
      </p>
    </div>
  </div>

  <!-- Project -->
  <div class="span2">
    <div class="picture">
      <a href="http://www.adobe.com/devnet/flex/articles/interactive_maps.html">
        <img src="img/training-building-interactive-maps-with-flex.jpg" alt=""/>
        <div class="image-overlay-link"></div>
      </a>
    </div>
    <div class="item-description">
      <h5>
        <a href="http://www.adobe.com/devnet/flex/articles/interactive_maps.html">Building interactive maps with Flex</a>
      </h5>
      <p>It has never been easier to build interactive online maps with Flex. There is a wide range of APIs now available. The focus of this article is building a simple map application using the
        open-source Modest Maps Flex API. Modest Maps offers a number of advantages over other Flex mapping APIs including the ability to point at multiple basemap providers and direct access to the
        source code.
      </p>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>